enterurl.com 2014-12-01

# ENTER URL

Privacy Policy

**EnterURL Privacy Policy**

**Summary**

EnterURL.com Values and respects the privacy of the Company's Customers and visitors. This statement discloses the information practices for the [EnterURL.com](http://www.enterurl.com/) and affiliated websites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, how to correct or change it and with whom the information is shared. These privacy practices apply only to online transactions, activity and to all email communications. **EnterURL.com will not sell your email address to anyone without your express permission and we control all email delivery to assure your privacy.** When we do share information with our partners and advertisers, it is in aggregate form, and does not identify you personally. EnterURL.com does not use any information about you except for the information that you provide or is publicly available, and this information is used solely to make the EnterURL services ("Services") provided more relevant to your interests. **Under no circumstances is your e-mail address ever shared with advertisers.** By becoming an EnterURL.com Customer, you agree to the EnterURL.com Services Agreement Terms and Conditions.

**1\. What Personally Identifiable Information Does EnterURL Collect?**   
In general, you can visit EnterURL.com on the Web without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we, or our Service partners, may need information from you in order to provide the requested Services. EnterURL’s primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful Services. EnterURL collects personally identifiable information when a Customer provides it to us, such as when you subscribe to Services, complete a survey, update your profile on our Web site, use certain Services, respond to our emails, and when you visit the EnterURL Web sites. EnterURL may also receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information you have provided to us. EnterURL has implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures, such as using encryption for transmission of credit card numbers, to help us keep your information secure, accurate, current, and complete. We will respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information.

**2\. What Anonymous Information Does EnterURL Collect?**  
We collect anonymous information from visits to our sites to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit and we also measure visitor activity on EnterURL.com and affiliated websites, but we do so in ways that keep the information anonymous. 

Also, when we collect personal data from you in connection with a transaction we may extract some information about that transaction in an anonymous format and combine it with other anonymous information. This anonymous information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner, you can either disable your cookies or opt-out of the Services and discontinue visits to the EnterURL and affiliates Web sites.

We collect the anonymous information we mentioned in the previous paragraphs through the use of various technologies, including "cookies". A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. Some EnterURL.com pages use cookies, sent by EnterURL.com or its third party service partners, or other technologies to better serve you when you return to the site. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some areas of some EnterURL web sites may not function properly. 

To track general Customer traffic patterns, we use electronic images known as single-pixel GIFs, transparent GIFs, or clear gifs. EnterURL.com also automatically receives and records information from our servers and from your browser including your IP address, the time, and information about the page you requested. In order to determine which features Customers find most useful, we use tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including: keeping count of return visits to our site or our advertisers' or partners' sites and accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate, statistical information on Web site and advertisement usage. 

EnterURL.com has certain companies help deliver ads and other online communications. These companies may collect and use information about customers to help us better understand the offers, promotions, and types of advertising that are most appealing to our customers. The information they collect is aggregated so it is not identifiable to a specific individual.

**3\. How Does EnterURL Use Information Gathered?**  
EnterURL uses the information we gather for the following purposes: 

**4\. How Does EnterURL Share The Information?**

  * To provide the EnterURL Services. 
  * To enhance the Customer experience we use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate Customer demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to build a better Service for you. 
  * To customize the promotions, advertising and content you see. 
  * To send Customers information about EnterURL as well as announcements, updates and other carefully screened special offers and promotions from EnterURL and our partners.

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
EnterURL.com will not sell your email address to anyone without your express permission and we control all email delivery to assure your privacy. However, EnterURL may share Customer information with affiliates. EnterURL.com will make your personally identifiable information available to other companies, individuals or other third parties under certain situations, such as when we have your consent to share the information and when we have engaged companies to work with or on behalf of EnterURL.com to provide a product or service that you have requested. When you request or use a service provided by one of our service partners within our network, you grant us permission to pass your registration information to that service partner. Their use of your information is subject to their applicable privacy policies. 

**Personalized URL Links**  
On occasion, EnterURL.com presents a personalized URL (link) that brings the visitor to a personalized Web page. Such a personal URL is readily identifiable and by clicking on that link and going to a personal Web page you are agreeing to let EnterURL.com collect information about your session visits. We use this information to help us provide you with information that matches your interests. If you do not wish information to be used in this way, do not click on such personalized URLs.

**Compliance With Laws and Communications with Legal Authorities**  
EnterURL responds to subpoenas, court orders and legal requests from authorities. We may contact the authorities if we believe that your actions violate applicable laws, EnterURL's Services Agreement Terms and Conditions , usage guidelines for specific products or services, threaten the rights, property or safety of EnterURL, our Customers, or others. 

**Business Relationships and Transfers**  
The EnterURL.com sites contain links to other websites. EnterURL.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites EnterURL is always seeking to improve our Web site, Services and features. In accomplishing these objectives, we may buy or sell a company, or one or more of the companies in our corporate family may merge with or be acquired by another company. If we sell a business, we may transfer some or all of your information as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue or for other business purposes.

**Aggregate Information**  
EnterURL aggregates personally identifiable information and discloses such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing, promotional and other purposes.

**5\. What Are Your Options?**  
Customers provide data requested by our sign-up and activation process. The Services Agreement Terms and Conditions requires Customers to receive certain communications related to the Services including announcements, updates and feature enhancements. If you do not wish to receive such communications, you may cancel your account and service on the EnterURL Web site or by following the instructions at the end of the e-mail you receive from EnterURL. If you do this, your service and account will automatically be terminated and you will receive no further service or contact from EnterURL. 

Technology will increasingly help you to have more control over your personal information. It will also help organizations to manage their privacy practices and policies. As an information technology provider, EnterURL.com actively supports the development of privacy technologies to help achieve these goals, and to help create greater trust and confidence in the way personal information is handled. Products and services are available which can help give you privacy protection while navigating the Web.

**6\. How Can You Update Your Personally Identifiable Information?**  
You can correct or change the information provided during sign-up / activation for any service. The instructions for making changes to your account can be found on the support page of the Web site. Customers may change this information at any time and as often as necessary by contacting customer support. 

**7\. How Will You Know If The Privacy Policy Is Changed?**  
By visiting the EnterURL Web site, becoming a Customer, or using the EnterURL Services, you hereby provide your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and are aware that our policy may change over time. Specifically, this Privacy Policy may be updated to reflect new features, Services and options, and any changes on the use of personal information. Continued use of the EnterURL Web site and its Services will indicate that you agree with any changes. Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected within this area of our Web site. 

**8\. Privacy of Children**  
Our Web site is not directed to children. As outlined in the Terms and Conditions, we do not knowingly permit registration by children and will not knowingly collect or use their personally identifiable information. 

**9\. Questions and Comments**  
Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the EnterURL.com Privacy Officer for clarification at [privacy@EnterURL.com](mailto:privacy@EnterURL.com) or write to:  
**Privacy Officer  
EnterURL.com  
381 Brinton Lake Road  
Thornton, PA 19373**
